deskaway.com 2014-11-22

# Privacy Policy | DeskAway

DeskAway is a product of Synage Software Pvt. Ltd (Synage Software). Synage Software is committed to protecting the privacy of its customers. This Privacy Policy outlines how we may gather and use information collected from our customers. 

**Information We Collect**  
When you register with DeskAway, you will be asked to provide certain personal information such as your name, time zone location and contact details. We may also ask you to provide additional personal information such as company name and title, that you may opt out of by not filling in the details on the form. 

We may also collect information about your usage of DeskAway, which includes but not limited to traffic statistics, date and time of visits, IP address, browser type, page visits etc. 

**Uses Of Your Information**  
Synage Software ensures that your information remains private and confidential. We will never use, sell, rent, exchange or share your information with any third parties. 

We will use your information for the following purposes: 

  1. To authenticate and provide you access to DeskAway.
  2. To notify you of change of services, maintenance notifications, information and promotional materials, newsletters from DeskAway.
  3. To improve our service and to track and diagnose problems. 
  4. To contact you for your reviews on the website and your experience with using DeskAway.
  5. To use it in our billing systems.

Synage Software will need to share the collected information when we must comply with the laws that require such disclosure to law enforcement authorities or other government parties. We may also share information in the case of an investigation, fraudulent or illegal activity on the site, violation of terms of use, and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person or our system. 

We reserve the right to use the name and/or logo of the company you work for in publicity material, advertising or marketing collateral, unless you specifically tell us otherwise. Your name, email address and all other personal information will remain confidential at all times. 

**Security**  
Synage Software employs security measures to protect your information from unauthorized. However, we cannot guarantee the security of your data while its being transmitted over the Internet to and from our servers. 

**Data Storage**  
Synage Software uses third party vendors and hosting providers to provide the necessary infrastructure, hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to operate DeskAway. Synage Software owns all the code, databases and all rights to the DeskAway application. You, as a customer will retain all rights to your data. 

**Public Forums/Blogs**  
Synage Software may create and host a public discussion forum or Blogs for its customers and the general public. Any information disclosed in these areas is deemed public information and each user is responsible for and should exercise caution when disclosing personal information on these forums/Blogs. Synage Software is not responsible for any such information disclosed or any action taken as a result of the disclosed information. 

**Cookies**  
Synage Software uses 'cookies' to store and track information about your usage on DeskAway. A cookie is information that is sent to your browser from the web server and stored on your computer. We issue cookies to your computer when you login to DeskAway and when you register with our service. Cookies are required to use DeskAway. 

**Changes To Our Privacy Policy**  
Synage Software reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. We will notify you of any significant changes through our website. 

**Contact**  
If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at [support@deskaway.com](mailto:support@deskaway.com)
